D-d-d-d-d-dumb-d-d-dum-dum-dumb-dumb
Dm-um-um-um-um
um-um-um-um-um
Dumb
dum-dum
First name UID last name 0
UID
In /etc/shadow, I'll make it clear. oh
you still sudo; I just *do* though.
Things I do, you ain't able.
Like Windows, you unstable.
enable, like Cisco -
not the rapper but the router.
Hit the bar, like the space, but in outer
where them girlies throwing digits after me -
efficient like Eratosthenes,
sievin' prime and inequal.
Sometimes I speak SQL.
I'm unequaled
L-L-M P-I-M-P
I'm multilingual.
Spit a `bar`? Nah, `foo`!
Parallel, superscalar, and virtual
NLP, Python, get it on, listen to me flow
all the wisdom I bestow;
maybe Bash, maybe Go.
By and large I undercharge .
My intellect -
don't bother doublecheck,
don't gotta guess or recollect.
Pop a shell, `strace` in your face.
Condition, I race.
whoami
/dev/zero, ui, uid, who?
last; who; w
(u)id 0
process hero
You knew then
I'm rootin'
no place like localhost
loopback this track
Find me back
in my home
dir
where the hard is
F-S-C-K, halt
F
S
C
K
While I grep, you just cat
Getting patched, I wrote that
with at
I hack,
you are a hack
I crack
and I'll be back
to smash
your stack
'cause you whack
Nah, you buggin'
debuggin' with print
no lint
bigint32
no, 64
UI? You I hack,
can't even crack
You just a bragger,
can't pir8 my swagger
Reppin' my seniority
top, highest priority
Can't `su` me,
I'm setuid
I won't ping back,
I'll just ack
Your request
at rest
'cause I'm the best
I'm a sinner, I syn/ack,
the stack winner,
an expert
You a beginner.
Wrote my first code in a Telnet session
You in a browser asking LLM questions
My systems uptime longer than your whole career
You sweat downtime, I drink beer
Your lame future becoming clearer
Backup - an old rsync mirror
What time it is?
Say that in UTC
Restart your job,
I'm automatically
I'm too bright
syntax highlight
SIGTERM, goodnight
my SIGKILL
you can't fight
exit(0)
justified every byte I write
kernel sing at ring 0,
like RAID you redundant
my skills are abundant
Like Windows, you unstable
What I do, you ain't able
Single disk, you high risk
I'm immutable, dutiful, and beautiful
my data, I never lose,
musical rollback, rewrite
Fork bomb, reuse
DROP your TABLE,
disable
flow control
XON, XOFF,
in ELF or COFF,
xterm X'd out.
Not pwning,
just a pawn,
already gone -
a null route,
logged out,
/dev/nulled
ya been culled
on UDP
IP on everything
like you,
kernel panic.
I'm not Satanic,
but a daemon -
always on.
You gone, did you hear?
I know you phear
my TCP.
On irc? #hack
while you on Slack or Discord,
you edgelord
umbilical Cat5
I cut your cord
now you wireless
and I'm tireless
coding for days
on three-phase
and DC
Like UDP
you unreliable,
it's undeniable
my checksums verifiable
$2^10 for two hours,
my root powers.
your beige towers
of shame
while you game
I work
you mechanical Turk
you barely earning.
I got ultra-wide SCSI disks still turning
15,000 RPM.
Nah son I build that from source,
Of course
you're confused
without that mouse that you use.
My keyboard's loud
been in the cloud
since before it had a name
netcat and Doom the only game
you lame mainframe
I got a PDP that runs VAX, VMS or RSTS.
RST your session;
DDOS your life, son
and fsck your wife, done.
yeah it's terminal
A little German'll...
Look:
she be with Hans Reiser
as in FS
from in DOS
she FAT
like my best synthesizer
kill -TERM
E_NOPERM
not your fault
you segfault, "yo, ops!?"
nah, /bk'd for life
no @ for your handle
Resign and light a candle,
FU U DIE.
Say goodbye
to that TT-
Y you running Windows?
My condolences, fam
Reboot twice just to fit it in RAM
BSOD? yeah: bitch, stop or die!
I run a headless slackware
just to flex on the sky
git pull
you a fool
every merge commit
makes someone on your team quit
Yo, I'm a SIGKILL assassin
you on mute
your password's cute
My alias is root;
my command absolute.
I execute
while you soft reboot,
your buffer overflowing
and I'm still going,
my stack's protected
I chown the throne,
now your shell rejected
Trying to fork, you getting SIGSTOP
Nothing left,
you got EOF
kill, nice, hangup, shutdown,
trap, abort,
break,
exec kill!